Lawrence Clark Powell papers, 1890-2001 (bulk, 1971-1991)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series XI: Arizona: A Bicentennial History, 1954-1987
  - Completed Draft (Pt. 2). No date (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Readers Responses Before Editing. No date (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Semifinal Draft. No date (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Final Draft. No date (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Draft Edited by Bert Fireman. 1975 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Final Draft. 1975 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Page Proofs. 1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Reviews. 1976-1978 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Pt. 1). 1968-1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Pt. 2). No date (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Series XII: Mysterious Transformation, 1992
  - Typed Draft (Pt.1). 1992 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Typed Draft (Pt. 2), Review by Book Club of California. 1992-1994 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Series XIII: Book Catalogs, 1950-1982
  - Book Catalogs. 1950-1982 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Series XIV: Video and Audio Tapes, 1976-1990
  - Video and Audio Tapes. No date, 1976-1990 (Box 32)
- Series XV: Awards, 1976-1989
  - Miscellaneous Awards. No date, 1976-1989 (Box 33)